eduwebconference.com 2008-06-16

# eduWEB - Conference 2006

**Privacy Policy**  

The eduWeb Conference is committed to protecting the privacy of your personal information. This Policy explains how we gather and use the information that we collect from the eduWeb site, located at http://www.eduwebconference.com. This policy may change over time. Amendments to this statement will be posted at this URL and will be effective when posted. Your continued use of this site following the posting of any amendment, modification or change shall constitute your acceptance thereof. 

**Communications:**  
The eduWeb Conference occasionally will contact registrants or members signed up for conference updates. Users can opt-out of such communications at any time by contacting Shelley Wetzel at [shelley@eduwebconference.com](mailto:shelley@eduwebconference.com). 

We may also employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include conference registration, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, and processing credit card payments. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.

In certain circumstances, we may share your contact information with sponsors. We also may provide information to regulatory authorities and law enforcement officials in accordance with applicable law or when we otherwise believe in good faith that the law requires it. 

**Use of Cookies**  
When you view our Web site we might store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a "cookie" or similar file. Cookies are small pieces of information stored on your hard drive, not on our site. Cookies do not spy on you or otherwise invade your privacy, and they cannot invade your hard drive and steal information. Rather, they help you navigate a Web site as easily as possible. 

We use cookies during the registration policy only. 

Because of our use of cookies, we can deliver faster service, consistent, updated results and a more personalized site experience. You have the option of setting your browser to reject cookies. However, doing this will hinder performance and negatively impact your experience on our site. 

**Public Forum**  
This eduWeb Site and affiliate (eduwebbuzz.com) site may make public chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to you from time to time. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose any personal information. 

**Children**  
We do not specifically collect online contact information from children nor do we target or sell products for purchase by children. 

**Security**  
This Web site has industry standard security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. While there is no such thing as "perfect security" on the Internet, we will take reasonable steps to insure the safety of your personal information. 

**Links to Other Web Sites**  
This Web site contains links to other Web sites. The eduWeb Conference is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. If you want to know the privacy policies of the other Web sites, please refer to the organization sponsoring such Web site. 

**Conference Sponsor Sites**  
Conference sponsors are responsible for their own policies and procedures. Review the sponsor's policy regarding their privacy policy. The eduWeb Conference is not responsible for products and services transactions that are consummated at third party Web sites. 

**Mail Lists**  
We use the information you provide about yourself for the in-print conference attendee listing and for a variety of organizational purposes, including sharing with you information about products and services we think might be of interest to you. We offer postal mailing lists to conference sponsors, but we do not sell, rent, or share e-mail addresses with external organizations or individuals.

**Consent**  
By registering for conference updates or signing up for the conference, you expressly consent to the collection and use by eduWeb Conference of personally identifiable information according to this Privacy Policy. 

The information may be used by the eduWeb Conference, or designated site partners (sponsors) to send you information and services that we think will be useful to you. 

**Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions**  
If you choose to visit eduWebconference.com, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this notice, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of North Carolina. If you have any concern about privacy at eduWebconference.com, please contact us with a thorough description, and we will try to resolve it. 

Our business changes constantly, and our Privacy Notice and the Conditions of Use will change also. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Notice applies to all information that we have about you. We stand behind the promises we make, however, and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers

**Opting Out of Receiving Communications**  
You may opt-out of receiving communications from eduWeb Conference by sending an email to [shelley@eduwebconference.com](mailto:shelley@eduwebconference.com)
